{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3836","name":"Greektown Casino - Fringe","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave","owner":"Greektown Casino","licenseNumber":"074069","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.04132,42.33457","geojson":{"id":"3836","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.041319668,42.33456876]},"properties":{"name":"Greektown Casino - Fringe","owner":"Greektown Casino","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"074069","establishmentid":"3836","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/12/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3829","name":"Greektown Casino - Monroe Market","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave"},{"establishmentid":"51622730","name":"Greektown Casino- Noodle Art","address":"555 E Lafayette"},{"establishmentid":"4478","name":"Greektown Casino - Josephine's","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave"},{"establishmentid":"4879","name":"Greektown Casino - GT Cafe","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave"},{"establishmentid":"5047","name":"Greektown Casino - Banquet Kitchen","address":"555 E Lafayette Ave"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44292","inspectionDate":"2018-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-202.12","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS shall be:    \r\n(A) Used according to:      \r\n(1) LAW and this Code,   \r\n(2) Manufacturer's use directions included in labeling, and, for a pesticide, manufacturer's label instructions that state that use is allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, (P)   \r\n(3) The conditions of certification, if certification is required, for use of the pest control materials, (P) and   \r\n(4) Additional conditions that may be established by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY; and\r\n(B) Applied so that:      \r\n(1) A HAZARD to EMPLOYEES or other PERSONS is not constituted, (P) and   \r\n(2) Contamination including toxic residues due to drip, drain, fog, splash or spray on FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES is prevented, and for a RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE, this is achieved by: (P)      \r\n(a) Removing the items, (P)   \r\n(b) Covering the items with impermeable covers, (P) or   \r\n(c) Taking other appropriate preventive actions, (P) and   \r\n(d) Cleaning and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS after the application. (P)  \r\n(C) A RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE shall be applied only by an applicator certified as defined in 7 USC 136 Definitions, (e) Certified Applicator, of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, or a PERSON under the direct supervision of a certified applicator. (Pf)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Under the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use according to manufacturer label directions."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"43667","inspectionDate":"2018-09-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"POP MACHINES","subLocation":"At the Pop Station","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42398","inspectionDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"40359","inspectionDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"Cleaning","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."}]},{"inspectionid":"38373","inspectionDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Ice bin","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Hand washing signage","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"36932","inspectionDate":"2016-10-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Ice machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE BAR","subLocation":"At the Sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3836"}}